







# Aron Smith

## Head of marketing

E-mail

info@buzzcv.com

Phone 07624 123456 Address

89 E 42nd St NY 10017 New York



# **Summary**

Marketing and business development professional with three years of skilled experience focusing on office organisation, marketing management, cost analysis, online marketing, customer relationship management, and planning and execution of the marketing strategy. Additional experience has been gained in the areas of staff responsibility, hiring, leadership, and project management.



# **Work experience**

2015 - Present

Head of marketing

Online marketing Company

Responsibilities include building the marketing organisation and managing the brand image and marketing for seven countries. Additional duties: negotiation and procurement of radio advertising, project management of the new front-end platform, cost analysis.

2013 - 2015 Webstation

Country manager

Tasked with the reorganisation and restructuring of the head office; this included increasing productivity, budgeting, contract negotiation as well as staff management and recruitment.

The standard 2011 - 2013

Marketing manager

Marketing manager for the UK markets. Major projects included drafting of the marketing plan, which was heavily focused on ROI, as well as strategising to achieve expansion on a limited budget.

Springify 2009 - 2011

**Operating Officer** 

Responsibilities included customer service, cash management, and development of the UK market, as well as trial-and-error marketing, investor relationship management, and customer service.

### Part time employment

- Budgeting Sweat company
- Telemarketing sales Realtalk sales
- Administration Huge banking
- Truck delivery sales Trucks N stuff



## **Education**

**Mount Saint Vincent University** 2008 - 2009

Courses

University of excellence 2002 - 2008

Master in business



# **Projects**

## Google AdWords certification

2014

Two week course to become a certified Google Adwords expert.

### Online marketing consultant

2013

A half year program specialising in online marketing.



## **Skills**

Marketing

Communication

Project management

Leadership



## Language

English Native Spanish Fluent Basic skills French



A natural leader and a master of marketing. That's how colleagues describe me. Personally, I would describe myself as a ambitious visionary who works hard to achieve my goals.

I'm an active person who loves adventures. Last year I decided that I would run a marathon and last month I achieved that goal. Now I'm ready to take on a new adventure but this time regarding my professional career.



#### William Smith

CEO
Buzzcv.com
example@buzzcv.com